看我来干掉你!
Now I'm gonna kill you!
呃 我要续杯
Uh, I need a refill.
- 你已经喝了三杯了,- 那又怎样?反正免费
- You've already had three.,- So what?They're free.
我要忙生日会,你自己去拿
I got a birthday.,Get it yourself.
难怪没人给他小费
No wonder he doesn'tget any tips.
好了...
All right...
献给ralphy生日舞要开始了
who's ready to singthe ralphy's,rumpusbirthday rump shake?
let's sing let's ridelet's bling,let's slide it's time for ralphy
let's sing, let's ridelet's bling,,let's slideit's time for ralphy
we'll dance, eat cake and do,the rump shake it's time for ralphy
we'll dance, eat cake and do,the rump shakeit's time for ralphy
你还好吗 伙计?
are you okay, man?
So hip-hooray'cause,ralphy wants to play
你还好吗?
you okay?
Stand up and cheer,for ralphy's here,let's spin, let's turnlet's wing, let's learn
it's time for ralphy--
好了好了,去休息下 快点
Okay, all right.,Let's get you in the back.Come on.
没事的 小朋友们,对不起了!
It's gonna be okay, kids.,Sorry!
-有心跳了,-Jack? Jack?
- Got a heartbeat.,- Jack?Jack?
-你们退后,-他是我哥哥
- I need youto step back.,- He's my brother.
Jack!,醒醒!
Jack!,Wake up!
打电话给你的父母,叫他们赶来princeton-plainsboro医院
Call your parents,tell them,to go to princeton-plainsboro hospital.
他们去世了
Our parents died.
他是我们唯一的亲人
He's all we've got.
我没有违法停车,我住在这里
I was not parked illegally.,I-I live here.
是Tritter探长的爱心小贴士
Love notefrom detective tritter.
心脏病发作
heart attack.
心脏插管显示没有器质性病变
His cath was cleanand echo showed,no structural abnormalities.
发作前有乏力 盗汗 体重下降症状
Fatigue, night sweats,weight loss,precededthe heart attack.
18岁的孩子 突然失去双亲,独自照顾两个弟弟妹妹
18-year-old kid,suddenly an orphan,and a single father of two.
五口之家!,不错的题材
Party of five!,Powerful stuff.
现代版橘子郡男孩
The O.C.Of its day.
压力可以解释一切症状除了脚癣
Stress explains everything,except the itchy feet.
脚气就会那样
Athlete's foot covers that.
服务生每天穿着帆布鞋工作12小时
Waiters work 12 hours a day,in old sneakers.
嗯 好啊,忽略掉症状 我们就轻松多了
Hmm, good idea.,Ignore the symptoms.Makes our job easy.
我没有忽略症状,我在分析症状
I'm not ignoringa symptom.,I'm explaininga symptom.
止吐治疗没有效果
kid's been hanging overa toilet,,despiteantiemetic therapy.
持续呕吐提示颅内压增高 肿瘤--
Persistent vomitingcould indicate,increased intercranial pressure,tumor--
心脏问题扯到脑子去了
sure.Heart problems.,It's gotta be the brain.
幸好这里有个神经科医生
Thank god there's a neurologistin the room.
是啊 如果我是足科医生就说是脚有问题
Right.It's the feet.,If only I were a podiatrist.
很可能从那群小毛孩那里感染了肠道病毒
Probably caughtan intestinal virus,from one of those feral kidsrunning around.
反复呕吐引起电解质紊乱
Repeated vomiting causes,an electrolyte imbalance,
导致心律失常 然后心脏病发
which leadsto an arrhythmia,,which leadsto the heart attack.
-还有脚癣,-不对
- And itchy feet.,- Nope.
就这样?,不对?
that's it?,Nope?
我已经给了很多提示了
I've saidtoo much already.
- 这不是游戏 house,- 的确不是 不过可以这么玩
- This isn't a game, house.,- No, it's not.But it could be.
-你在写什么?,-没什么
- What are you writing?,- Nothing.
如果你知道诊断 干吗不--
If you know the diagnosis,why don't--
不把你扔下水怎么学得会游泳?
how are you gonnalearn to swim unless I take off,your floaties and throw you into shark-infested waters?
你只翻了下病历 不可能作出诊断
You can'tknow what's wrong,after a 30-second perusalof his file.
- 那是你不能,- 游戏怎么能没有规则呢?
- Apparently you can'T.,- Now, what's a gamewithout rules?
不准反扑，不准咬人,每人可以做一个检测
No, tag-backs, no biting.,You get one test each.
午饭时间截止
And the clockruns until lunch.
如果我是对的 他就能活下去,如果我想错了 游戏就很残酷了
If I'm right,he'll still be alive.,If I'm wrong,this is a very cruel game.
游戏的名字叫"脚癣"
The Game Is A Itchy Foot
你迟到了 我从你预约的时间开始计费
You're late.I charge for the time,you were supposed to be here.
Tritter拖走了我的车
Tritter towed my car.
他冻结了我的财产,他要彻底整垮我
He's frozen my assets.,He's on a crusade.
你现在涉及一桩毒品案
You're a person of interest,in a narcotics investigation.
和他们的嫌疑犯有牵连
You're linked to their suspect,and his activities.
我不是大毒枭pablo escobar疯狂的追随者
I'm not pablo escobar'sevil henchman,cruising into miamiin a cigarette boat.
我只不过是个给病人开止痛药的医师
I'm a physician who prescribed,vicodin to a pain patient.
这个警察传真给我报告,说在他家找到600片止痛药
This police reportyou faxed me,saysthey found 600 pillsin his apartment.
- 都是你开的?,- 他是慢性疼痛
- You prescribed those?,- He's in chronic pain.
- 这明显是滥用权力,- 是或不是?
- This is obviouslyan abuse of power.,- Is that a yes or no?
病人用药多年后会有耐药性
Patients build up,a tolerance over the years.
这是他伪造处方的最好动机
Perfect motive for him,to forge those scrips.
- 你还是没回答我的问题,- 怎么 我们在练习对质吗?
- I still don't have an answer.,- What, are we, like,role playing?
是啊 不过你表现很差
Yeah.,And you suck at it.
而且不幸的是 你假装是你开的
Which is reallyunfortunate,,because you'repretending to be you.
我要上庭了
I gotta get to court.
Michael告诉我 你可以帮我弄回车子
Michael told me you could,help me get my car back.
打离婚官司的律师怎会了解麻醉品管制
Yeah, divorce lawyersusually know,the ins and outsof drug enforcement.
你想要回车子,就得告诉警察他们想要的
You want your car back,you're gonna,have to givethe cops what they want.
多谢 我是病急乱投医
Thanks.Usually people feel,helplessin these situations.
House医生很可能要坐牢
Dr. House is probablygoing to jail.
如果你继续做伪证,就要跟他一起蹲班房了
You keep on lying for him,,you'll go right along with him.
House看这一页的时候露出了,“我是天才”的死脸
House was on this page when he got that,annoying"I'm such a genius" look.
- 写了什么?,- 病史
- What's there?,- Patient history.
他18岁了,可能抽烟 喝酒 吸大麻
He's 18.,Probably drinks,smokes, does drugs.
我猜中了多少?
How close am I?
自从他父母去世就戒毒戒酒了
Quit drugswhen his parents died.,Quit smoking.
House并没有嘲笑我的诊断,他只是说不对
House didn't mockmy viral idea.,He just saidit was wrong.
也就是说他不想告诉我原因
Which means he didn't,want to give reasons.Which means,
也就是说也许我接近正确答案了
I must have been close.
那我考虑一下细菌感染
I'm thinking bacterial.
我去做血培养
I'm doing a blood culture.
那我做磁共振
I am doing an mrI.
如果是脑肿瘤的话,午饭之前就会出现脑疝
It there was a tumor,intercranial pressure,could cause his brainto herniate before lunch.
- 跟你做的压力检测是一回事,- 所以我不打算做
- Same thing withyour stress test.,- Which is whyI'm ditching it.
- 那你做什么?,- 不告诉你
- What are you doinginstead?,- Not telling.
说真的--你要玩这个游戏?
Seriously--you playing his game?
既然不得不玩, 那不妨享受一下
We're all playing his game.,Might as well enjoy it.
工作时其他人有不舒服吗?
Anybody else sick at work?
我之前肚子痛
I had a stomach achebefore him.
不是你的错 will,继续写作业吧
This isn't your fault, will.,Keep working.
我哥哥住院了,Collier老不会在意我有没有完成作业
My brother's in the hospital.,Mrs. Collier won't careif I finish my homework.
但是你哥哥在意
Your brother cares,if you finish your homework.
我可以做你假象的朋友吗?
Can I be your imaginaryfriend?
他是医生
He's a doctor.
脚怎么样了?,还痒吗?
How are the feet?,Still itch?
重要吗?
is that important?
我不知道,你觉得呢?
I don't know.,Is it?
你磕什么药?
What kinds of drugsyou into?
你现在可以不用说那个
You don't have to talk,about that right now.
不 没关系,我跟他们之间没有秘密
No, it's okay.,I don't keep secretsfrom them.
他们知道我之前磕药
They know I did drugs,before our parents died.
聪明 承认过去 否认现在
Clever.Admit the past.,Deny the present.
我现在戒了 我要养两个孩子
I'm clean.,I'm raising two kids.
不然就太不负责了 不是吗?
It'd be pretty irresponsible,wouldn't it?
告诉8岁的小孩这些好吗?
But confiding in an,eight-year-old is okay?
如果我对他们敞开心扉,他们也会这样对我
If I'm open with them,,then they'll be open with me.
的确 拳击里也有这种战术
Yeah.Turning the other cheek's,a good strategy in boxing.
小孩撒谎不是因为不信任你
Kids don't lie because,they got trust issues.
他们有事隐瞒才撒谎
They lie because they,got something to hide.
看他 坐在这里什么都没做 还撒谎
Look at him,sitting there doing nothing,,and he's still lying.
我们从不欺骗jack
We don't lie to jack.
- 你拼写测验不及格而且忘记--,- 没有
- Spelling test you failedand forgot to--,- no.
- 数学测验呢?,- 没有
- Math test?,- No.
跟同桌打架?
Fight with the kid,sitting next to you?
他不是我同桌
He doesn't sit next to me.
- 另一个可能已经有性经验了,- 我没有!
- The other one's probablyhaving sex.,- I am not!
现在没有 等你有的时候就会撒谎了
Yet.When you start,,you're gonna lie about it.
- 离答案远着呢,- 我没参加游戏
- Colder.,- I'm not playing.
不要动 jack,不要很久的
Keep very still for me,jack.,This won't take long.
你一次磕多少?
How much dopedid you smoke?
- 他一定要在这吗?,- 不 忽略他
- Does he have to be here?,- No.Ignore him.
- 不是肺的问题,- 我又没说是
- It's not his lungs.,- I never said it was.
那抽烟呢?
What about the cigarettes?
你怎么戒掉的?,口香糖 膏药 还是催眠治疗?
How did you quit?,Gum, patch, hypnosis?
他从每两包到突然不抽,突然戒断
He went from two packs,to nothing, cold turkey.
不然我也可以跟你闲聊
Or we could justmake small talk.
你还和儿科那个护士约会?
You still seeingthat nurse in pedes?
我觉得她不适合你
I just don't think she's right for you.
你应该找个...,没感情 爱算计 有野心的
You need someone...,detached, calculating,ambitious.
你要找的就是穿裙子的你
You need yourselfin a skirt.
-Jack 他要问你个问题,-我并没有真的戒掉
- Jack, he asked youa question.,- I didn't really quit.
只是有点忽然觉得无味了
I just sort of lost taste for it.
有意思
Interesting.
听起来可以算一种症状
Sounds like one of those,symptom thingies.
他还是呕吐 心脏病和脚癣
He's still puking,and he had,a heart attackand itchy feet.
- 不关肺的事,- 我没说是啊
- It's not his lungs.,- I never said it was.
显而易见啊
Ice cold.
我现在注射麦角新碱
I'm injecting ergonovine,to see if your heart attack
看你的心脏病是不是血管痉挛引起的
was caused by a spasm in the vessels,surrounding your heart.
如果你不舒服...说一声
Let me know if anything,feels...unusual.
如果是心脏的问题,为什么那个医生要检查我的大脑?
If the problem's around my heart,,why did that other doctorlook at my brain?
是啊 为什么那个医生要检查他的大脑?
Yeah, why did that other doctor,look at his brain?
我们只是要排除其他一切可能的病因
We're justtrying to eliminate,as many possibilitiesas we can.
因为你认为是血管痉挛引起心脏病,你就要再次诱导痉挛?
So because you thinkthe spasm caused his,heart attack,you're gonnainduce another spasm.
你赞成这样做吗?
Did you consent to this?
一切都在掌控中
everything's under control.
测试可以发现那些动脉受累,我们就能修复它们
Tests are gonna identifywhich arteries,are affectedso we can repair them.
仿佛不起作用啊
Your meds don't seemto be doing anything.
要不就是你想错了, 要不就是,身体所受的压力还不足以导致痉挛
So either you're wrong,or his system,hasn'tbeen pushed enoughto set anything off.
你想回家 对吧?
You wanna get back home,right?
我是说你也许已经很久没有打扫房子,交水电费了
I mean, you're probably already,falling behindwith the housework, the bills.
你认为请多久的病假才会被开除呢?
How many sick daysdo you think,you'll getbefore they replace you?
心率增快 其它正常
Heart rate's up,but nothing else.
如果我真的病了 他们不能开除我
They can't fire meif I'm sick.
是啊 你无可取代
Right, you'reirreplaceable.
除了你还有谁适合跟兔子跳舞呢?
Who else would they findqualified,to dance with a rodent?
你怎么养活一家人?
How can you even support your family?
小孩子衣服不合穿了怎么办?,生病了怎么办?
What happens when those kidsgrow,out of their clothes,when they get sick?
还是没有痉挛
Still no spasm.
孩子会被人带离你身边的 jack
They'll take those kidsaway from you, jack.
或许我现在就该带他们过来 跟你告别
Maybe I should bring themin here right now,so that you cankiss them good-bye.
你看不出来他心脏是好的吗?!,别折磨他了!
Can't you seehis heart is fine?!,Stop torturing him!
你是什么医生啊?
What kind of doctorare you?
很好 非常感谢,好的 再见
wonderful, thank you so much.,Okay, bye.
- 你刚来?,- 巴士烂透了
- You're just getting here?,- Buses suck.
- 你的车呢?,- 做抵押了
- Where's your car?,- It's a hostage.
Tritter想要我做反证
Tritter wants me to testifyagainst house.
- 你不会那么做的,- 这是提问还是命令?
- You're not going to.,- Is that a questionor an order?
任何罪名都可吊销house的执照
Any sort of conviction,willcost house his license.
是会影响医院吧
Which will costthis hospital.
放松点 我不会害你手下的红人
Relax, I'm not gonna mess,with your precious resource.
我跟律师说叫tritter去死
I told my lawyer to tell tritter to go to hell.
Marco!
为什么我的处方都被退回来了?
Why are all my prescriptions,getting bounced back?
不好意思Wilson医生  我想通知你的,你手机放哪了?
Sorry, dr. Wilson.I was trying to call you.,Where's your phone?
在车里 我的病人都在这等着用药呢
In my car.My patients,on the other hand,,are here and neededtheir medications.
对不起 我不能那么做,你的处方权被暂时吊销了
I'm sorry, I can'T.,Your dea number'sbeen suspended.
怎么这么沮丧?
why so sad?
Chase还有机会答对
There's still a chance,that chase got it right.
刚才真是紧张的两秒钟
Oh!That was suspenseful,for about two seconds.
血培养细菌阴性
Blood culturewas negative for bacteria.
甲肝阳性?
Positive for hepatitis a?
不知道谁给加了这项测试
Hmm, I wonder who could have,ordered that extra test.
那个人一定知道 持续呕吐
Must be somebody who knew,what persistent vomiting,
突然对尼古丁丧失味觉,和脚癣的共通处
sudden distaste for nicotine,and itchy feethave in common.
甲肝不能解释心脏病
Hep a doesn'texplain the heart attack.
的确不能 但像chase说的 呕吐可以
No, but as chaseso deftly,pointed out earlier,puking does.
而甲肝可以引起呕吐
And hep a explains the puking.
如果这真的关乎性命而不只是游戏...
If this had been real life,instead of just a game...
药品管理局撤销了我的处方权
the dea st revoked,my prescription privileges.
那谁给我开药?
Who's gonnaprescribe my vicodin?
对 所以我来这告诉你 你倒大霉了
Yes, well,that's why I'm here.,This is a disaster for you.
放松点
Relax.
Tritter没办法了 他拿不出证据
Tritter's just getting desperate.,He's got no real evidence.
他要逼得你背叛我
He's trying to squeeze youinto ratting.
我不能让他逼死我的病人
I'm not gonna let him,squeeze my patients.
他们没事的
They'll be fine.
再说你开的抗癌药又没什么用
Most of your cancer medicine,sucks anyway.
我想让你们帮我开处方 直到这事过去
I'm gonna use your teamto do,my prescribingtill this is straightened out.
一下子没有戏剧化的效果了
Suddenly this doesn't seem,nearly as dramatic.
给那孩子IVIG治疗(静注免疫球蛋白),治好他 放他走
Go pump ivig into the kid.,Cure him and get him out of here.
甲肝?
Hep a?
不是,"Chase"血培养细菌
No.,"Chase,"blood test for bacteria.
"Foreman M.R.I.",太固执而不检查肺部
"Foreman, M.R.I."Too stub born,to check the lungs.
Cameron 好尝试 可惜没有痉挛
Cameron, nice try.,No spasm".
"但是公主坐着坐着坐着"
"but the princess,sat and satand sat".
假装听不到
Pretending not to listen,
假装在本子上写着日记
pretending to write in her journal,with the flowers on it.
假装不喜欢八岁小孩拯救地球的故事
Pretending she didn't likestories,about eight-year-oldswho save the world.
我11了
I'm 11.
所以你就不能拯救地球了
Which is why you can,no longer save the world.
-我八岁,-Yeah
- I'm eight.,- Yeah.
我们就全靠你了
We're all completely dependent on you.
-早上好!,-早上好
- Mornin'!,- Mornin'.
好消息,我们可以撤除IVIG治疗
Good news.,We can take you off the ivig.
甲肝病毒已经清除了
The hep a has cleared your system.
-你明天就可以出院了,-Yeah!
- You'll be good to goby tomorrow.,- Yeah!
我怎么被传染的呢?
How do you thinkI got it?
可能吃了不干净的食物
It could have been contaminated food.
也可能是清理卫生间的时候
It could have been from,cleaning bathrooms at work.
还可能...
Or it could have been...
别担心,他们已经听到了
don't worrY.,They've heard it all.
肛交也很常见
Anilingus is a common way.
你得告诉那些人你有甲肝,叫他们也去做检查
You should just tell the people that you've,dated they shouldget themselves checked.
别担心 我太忙了 没时间跟他们做
Don't worry, I've been too busy,chasing after these guysto go spelunking.
你真恶心
You're gross.
我认为
I think.
- 你手疼吗?,- 不疼 弟弟
- Does your arm hurt?,- Arm's fine, bro.
- 那为什么出血了呢?,- 不是出血 是...
- Then why is it bleeding?,- It's not, it'S...
把手举过头顶
raise your armabove your head.
你的耳朵
Your ear.
还有鼻子
And your nose.
凝血酶原时间和凝血激酶时间延长,确定凝血异常
high pt and ptt on jack's blood,panel confirm a coagulopathy.
那么...,我们治好了甲肝...
So...,we cure the hep A...
又有其它问题出来了,有意思
and something else pops up.,Interesting.
什么感染可以导致DIC?,(弥散性血管内凝血)
What infections cause dic?
你还好吗?
You okay?
我在幻想中踢球的时候弄伤了肩膀
I hurt my shoulder playing,fantasy football.
我们是要讨论引起dic的原因,还是要让那孩子继续受罪?
Shall we discuss what causes dic,,or shall we just send the kidback to his miserable life?
- 他没有受罪,- 是哦
- He's not miserable.,- Right.
知道父母去世了自己也快完了,还兴奋得发抖
He's thrilledthat his parents,are deadand his life is over.
餐厅可能有大量大肠杆菌,艾肯菌和链球菌
The restaurant's probablyteeming with E.,Coli,eikenella, and strep.
孩子的饭前便后没有洗手--
Kids don't wash their hands,between the pottyand the party, and--
或者是食物中毒,Jack每天都在那里吃饭工作
or it's a food-borne toxin.,Jack eatsat that cesspool every day.
但是只有Jack得病了
Jack's the only onewho got sick.
一个有纹身 穿环,和可能不洁性生活史的孩子
Kid's got tattoos, piercings, and probably,some nasty little girlloaned him the hep A.
也可能感染梅毒或淋病
Could have also given him,syphilis or gonorrhea.
-我要一个人,-cameron去吧
- I need one of you.,- Take cameron.
反正你的主意也很傻
Your idea was dumb, anyway.
Chase 我要你回那家餐厅,把他的呕吐物带回来
Chase, I need youto head back to that,cesspooland get me the kid's puke.
Foreman 做一个腰穿,排除cameron说的不洗手理论
Foreman, do an lp, and have cameron,run downthat potty/party theory.
为什么不能直接检查他?
Why don't ijust test him?
我们私下说
Let's not discuss thisin front of the help.
他大量呕吐
The amount of vomitingthat kid did,
血液中能查出毒素的可能性小
wouldn't be enough toxinsleft,in this systemto show up in his blood.
他在这都吐厕所里而不是别人身上
Since he vomitedinto the toilet,hereinstd of on somebody,
所以只有去餐厅才能找到病原体
that restaurant is our only,source of essential vomit.
你不能在foreman面前说这些吗?
And you couldn't say that,in front of foreman?
不 我不能在foreman说这个
No, I couldn't say this in front of foreman.
我要开药
I need a refill.
tritter知道我以前给你开过
Detective tritter knows about,the scrips I wrote before.
正因如此,你现在停止, 就显得可疑了
Exactly.,If you stop now,it'll look suspicious.
- 有人被这个理由骗到吗?,- 开处方
- Does anyone fallfor that argument?,- Write the scrip.
不
No.
一张处方不会让你--
One prescription,isn't gonna make you--
我们都知道不可能只有一张
we both knowit's not,gonna be just one.
我宁愿没工作也不能没执照
I'd rather lose my job,than lose my license.
Daniel silvers 前列腺癌,开非格司亭 两周的剂量
Daniel silvers,prostate cancer,,needs filgrastim,two-week supply.
Andrea donavan 乳腺癌,继续开甲地孕酮
Andrea donavan,breast cancer,,just needs her refill of her megestrol.
- 你没写,- 你想让我写?
- You're not writing.,- You want me to write?
你可以打电话叫他们来
Well, you couldphone them in.
但是最终还是要写的
But eventually, yeah,probably somebody's,gonna wantsomething written down.
- 我没见过这些人,- 我见过
- I haven't met these people.,- I have.
- 我做了检查 下了诊断,- 我知道
- I've diagnosed themand everything.,- I know.
- 我知道 不是我不信任你,- 是我诊断的
- I know, I'm not sayingI don't trust you.,- Just my diagnosis.
但是我开的处方 我--
These are gonna bemy prescriptions, I--
他们是我的病人!
they're my patients!
- 我开处方,- 署我的名字!
- My prescriptions.,- My name!
那个Tritter会查的
That tritter will readon the scrip.
他想让你受罪,你认为他会置之不理吗?
He wants to make you miserable.,You don't thinkhe's gonna ask questions?
有什么工作是只有jack做的吗?
Is there anything jack does that no one,else does?Any special duties?
没有 我们有很多收碗的
No, we got lotsof bussers.
你们用什么清洁剂?
What kind of cleaning,products do you use?
成天都有小孩跑来跑去,什么都往嘴里放
Well, we got a bunchof kids running around,sticking everythingin their mouths.
所以我们不能用有毒的
So we can't useanything toxic.
这就是了 星期一的垃圾
That's it.,Monday's trash.
没有人可以帮忙...,把这个袋子弄出来?
So there's no one who canmaybe...,help get the bags out?
对不起 人手短缺
Sorry, short-handed.
我给小费
I can tip.
我肯定jack的呕吐物,在蓝色垃圾袋里的那包礼物上
I'm pretty sure jack's pukeis in,the blue trash bagwith the wrapped gifts.
但是如果你找到有意大利面的,就不是他的
But if you find spaghetti,,that's the wrong vomit.
我还要等多久才能拿到药?
How much longer do I have,to stay on this medication?
我一天到晚都想吐
I mean, I'm nauseousall the time.
或许我还是应该用他莫昔芬
Maybe I should go backon the tamoxifen.
你用了阿纳曲唑好了很多 beth
You're doing so much better,on the anastrozole, beth.
我不想让你换药
I'm reluctantto make a change.
我现在不能陪女儿玩
I can't playwith my daughter.
或者是接她放学
Or pick her up from school.
我晚上不能起来帮她盖好被子
I can barely get up,and tuck her in at night.
肯定有别的办法
There's got to besomething else.
她是谁?
Who is she?
你知道 这是个教学医院
Well, as you know,,this is a teaching hospital.
- 她是个学生?,- 不 我是医生 今天协助wilson医生
- She's a student?,- No, I'm a doctor.I'm assisting dr.wilson today.
怎么了 你认为他的诊断不对?
Why, do you think he got,my diagnosis wrong?
- 不 我确定--,- 不 不
- No, I'm sure--,- no, no.
她只是在查看我的处方
She's just consulting,regarding my prescriptions.
你认为他开的药不对?
You think he gotmy meds wrong?
- 不 只是--,- 不是
- No, it's just--,- no.
那她在这干吗?
Then why is she here?
你现在在做什么?
What are you doing now?
我要抽取你哥哥的一点脊髓液做样本
I'm gonna get a sample of,your brother's spinal fluid.
- will在哪?,- 学校
- Where's will?,- School.
这疼吗?
Is that gonna hurt?
这可以帮助我们诊断他得了什么病
It's gonna help us figure out,what's making him sick.
- 你不是也该上学吗?,- 老师休息
- Shouldn't yoube in class too?,- Teacher work day.
只有你? will的老师不休?
For you, but not will?
是 我也没想通
Yeah, it didn't make sense to me either.
我能帮忙吗?
Can I help?
我想比叫护士快点
Well, I guess it's quicker,than calling a nurse.
还有查课的教务主任
And a truant officer.
来 抓住他的小腿,把膝盖朝胸部弯
Here, grab his shins.,Push his knees uptowards his chest.
就这样抓紧了
Now hold him there tight.
护士就做这些?
This all nurses do?
我上司不信任他们做别的
My boss doesn't trust 'em,to do anything else.
他会死吗?
Is he gonna die?
不 没人会死的
No.,No one's gonna die.
世界上所有的人都不会?,那太好了
In the whole world, ever?,That's so great.
- 我的意思是--,- 我懂你的意思
- Well, I meant--,- I know what you meant.
但我也知道总有坏事发生
But I also know bad thingsdo happen.
我爸爸出门总爱喝上两杯
My dad always had a few drinkswhen they went out.
说这样开车没事
Always saidhe'd be okay to drive.
直到出事
Until he wasn'T.
我这次需要提前做好心理准备
I would just likesome warning this time.
现在没有那样的迹象 知道吗?
We're nowhere nearanything like that,happening right now.Okay?
把他翻过来
Let's scoot himback over.
怎么了?!,你做了什么?
What was that?!,What'd you do?
-你弄断了他的肋骨?,-就轻轻的碰了下
- You broke his rib?,- Barely touched him.
就是说--ow!
Which means--ow!
-就是这里,-弄好它
- Found it.,- Fix it.
骨髓炎 感染已经侵犯到骨头了
Osteomyelitis.Means the infection's,spread to his bones.
那就意味着细菌或病毒感染  而且  ---
Which means it's either,bacterial or viral,and that--ow!
我请你来是解除痛苦的,你是不是理解反了?
I hired youto take away the pain.,Is there some confusion?
你有没有想过换只手用拐杖?
You ever thought aboutusing,your caneon the proper side?
是啊  那就是问题所在
Yeah, that's the issue.
星期五晚上 我的拐杖,突然发现自己一直在错误的一边
Friday night,my cane suddenly,noticed it was on the wrong side.
- 你能给我开些止痛药吗?,- 不行
- Can you score mesome vicodin?,- No.
我做了针吸活检,去检查--
I did a needle aspiration,to confirm which--
培养还得多长时间---  啊!
how long till the cultures--gaaah!
为什么非要在我说话的时候那么用力?
Why do you only do thatwhen I'm talking?
你的肩膀需要放松
You gottarest your shoulder.
我们得给你来件别的装备
And we're gonna get you,on some different equipment.
- 拐杖不错,- 别以为我不知道你的意思
- Nice cane.,- If I know what you mean?
- Chase 你可以停下拉,- 我快完成了
- Chase, you can stopdoing that.,- I'm almost finished.
他得的是骨髓炎
He's got osteomyelitis.
说明不是食物中毒
Means you're wrong aboutfood-borne toxins.
而且 你也可以停下了
And...,you can stop too.
- 梅毒,- 你确定?
- Syphilis.,- You sure?
看看结果
Read the printouT.
他的艾肯菌培养也呈阳性
He's also positivefor eikenella.
你们其中一个搞砸了
One of you two screwed up.
- 没有,- 不可能
- No.,- Not a chance.
要么小伙子病的比我们想象中严重
Or this kid is a lot sicker,than we thought.
继续你的检测
Finish that test.
一个问题不可能有2个正确答案
It should be impossible to get,two right answersto one question.
不会有3个吧?
Is it okay to have three?
很显然  他还肉毒杆菌中毒
Apparently.,He's positive for botulism too.
我们消灭1个感染后又冒出来3个
so...we knock down one infection,and three more pop up.
游戏有作弊嫌疑
I think this game is rigged.
Jack?,来人!
Jack?,Somebody help!
我们把他体内的3种病毒都杀灭了
we've managed to clear all,three infections out of his system.
但是他现在每个几个小时抽搐一次
But now he's having seizures,every few hours.
他已经免疫失调
He's gotta beimmuno-compromised.
不是 白细胞数量正常,艾滋病病毒检测呈阴性
No, white count was normal,,and he was negativefor hiv.
如果他不是免疫失调,那他为什么看起来像是呢?
Well, if he's notimmuno-compromised,,why is he acting likehe's immuno-compromised?
抽搐能说明什么?
What do the seizures tell us?
什么都说明不了,CT检查没有结构性的病变
Nothing, there were no,structural abnormalitieson the ct,
没有神经上的病灶 没有电解质不平衡,什么都没有
non-focal neuro-exam,,no electrolyte imbalance,nothing.
通常18岁的小伙子,莫名抽搐的原因有哪些?
What do unexplainedseizures and,really sick18-year-oldshave in common?
你觉得是外伤?
You thinking trauma?
我是说毒品
I'm thinking drugs.
他承认服用过
He's an admitted user.
毒品毁了他的免疫系统
Drugs trashedhis immune system.
毒理检查为阴性
Tox screen was clean.
毒理检查呈阴性只能说明,他的血液和尿液里不含毒品
Clean tox screen meansthere's no,drugsin his blood or urine.
可能他体内的脂肪残留着,"风华"岁月时的东西
There couldstill be drugs trapped,in his fat cellsfrom the good ol' days.
如果是脂肪细胞内残留,为什么到现在才有影响?
If they're in his fat,,why would they beaffecting him now?
一个敏锐的观察家才会注意到,他最近有消化问题
A keen observerwould notice,that he's had somedigestive issues lately.
他的体重锐减会分解脂肪,有毒物质会重新释放到他的体内
His weight loss could haveburned off,fat cellsand released the drugsback into his system.
那可没法知道,没办法检验脂肪细胞的毒理性质
there's no way to know.It's impossible,to test fat cells for drugs.
让他的体重再降点也不是不可能
It's not impossibleto make him lose more weight.
你想让他饿着,以次引发抽搐或是心脏病
You want us to starve himso we can drive him,into another seizure,and maybe a heart attack,
只是为了做毒理检验?
just so we can runanother tox screen?
那太残忍了,让他出汗不就行拉
That'd be cruel.,Just sweat it out of him.
我父母死后我就再也没有碰过毒品
I haven't touched a thing,since the night my parents died.
药会在你体内残留很长时间
Drugs stay in your systema long time.
当警察告诉我们父母发生了车祸,我刚吸完毒...
I was high...the night the cops came,to tell us what happened.
你知道他们告诉我时,我的第一个反映是什么吗?
You know the first thing,I didwhen they told me?
我大笑
I laughed.
他们死后,我就不是原来的我
I'm not the person I was,when they died.
我真希望他们能知道
I wishthey could see that.
他们在泉下一定有知,一定以你为骄傲
Well, I'm surethey're watching,,and I'm surethey're proud.
Will的辅导员就是一直跟他那么说的
That's what will's guidance,counselor keeps telling him.
你怎么告诉他的?
What do you tell him?
我和他说那是瞎话
I tell him it's crap.
我们的父母活在我们的记忆里,他们死了
Our parents live onin our memories,,but they don't live on.
- Jack?,- 按住他
- jack?,- hold him still!
- 别折断了他的胳膊,- 断了还可以接
- Don't break his arm.,- We'll fix it.
血样要紧
We need to get a sample.
House,坏消息
House.,Bad news.
瞧瞧你
Look at yoU.
怎么不派Cameron下来,到有空调的走廊来送坏消息
Couldn't havesent cameron down hereto this,air-conditioned hallwayto deliver the bad news?
Jack又抽搐了 但是血液检查没事,完全没有毒品残留
Jack seized again,but his blood was clean.,Completely drug-free.
那么他只是碰巧在,我们逼他进桑拿房时抽搐?
So he just happenedto have a seizure,at the exact timethat we stuck him in a sauna?
绝不是巧合
It's not a coincidence.
不论我们让不让他进桑拿他还是,会每隔几小时就抽搐一次
He's still seizingevery few hours,,whether we stick himin a sauna or not.
噢 天哪!,你为什么用那个?
Oh, my god!,Why are you using that?
我用了好几年了
I've had it for years.
不 那会--损伤你的肩膀
No, that's--that's gonna,make your shoulder hurt.
你该用这个
You need one of these.
他是 个..,医生..
He's A...,doctor.
- 他还没感染?,- 我看快了
- Is he stillinfection-free?,- I'm sure not for long.
我早说过造成抽搐是其他原因而不是感染
My point being that somethingother,than those infectionscaused these seizures.
也就是说他脑袋有问题,给他做扫描
That means there'ssomething,in his head.Scan him.
- 扫描过了,- 那是以前做的
- We scanned him.,- Well, that was then.
以前的不算数,小孩子很多变 再做一次
This is not then.,Kid keeps changing.Scan him again.
Cameron在哪?
Where is cameron?
我不会给你开维柯丁
I'm not writing youa scrip for vicodin.
我就剩下2片了
I've only gottwo pills left.
切成两半,这样的话你就有4片了
Cut 'em in half.,Then you'll have four.
你替Wlison开处方 Wilson给我开处方,快开一个
You're prescribing for wilson.,Wilson prescribes for me.Write up a scrip.
你知道自己的麻烦
You knowyou have a problem.
有个戴警徽的整天围着我转
Yeah, it's got a badgeand everything.
- 你用药太多--,- 是啊! 你是对的
- You're taking too much--,- fine!You're right.
那什么才是适量的?
What's the correct amount?
就写个适量的处方
Write up a scripfor the correct amount.
说不出?
No answer?
因为这个根本没什么可争论
That's 'cause we're having,the wrong debate.
这和我的麻烦无关,而是你在回避我
This has got nothing to dowith my problem,and everything to dowith you avoiding a problem.
你害怕开了处方给我,会像Wilson那样麻烦缠身
You're afraid that if youwrite me a prescription,,you're gonna wind uplike wilson.
我当然会怕
Of course I am.
Tritter想叫我痛苦
Tritter wants to winby giving pain.
难道你想成为帮凶吗?
Do you really wantto be a part of that?
作为一个医生 你怎么能那样做?
As a doctor,how do you do that?
接着,能帮你顶一阵
Here.,This'll tide you over.
用来消除我的经前综合症,应该对你也有点用处
If it can take the edgeoff my pms,,it should do wonders for you.
为什么你们还要检查我的头部?
Why are you lookingat my head again?
抽搐通常意味着神经上的一些病变
Seizures usually indicate,something neurological.
我不会好起来了,是不是?
I'm not gonna get better.,Am I?
检查之后才能下结论
We'll know moreafter the test.
我得找个能照顾Will和Kama的人
I've gotta find out who can,take care of will and kama.
我们别太悲观了 好吗?
Let's not get aheadof ourselves, okay?
你会痊愈的 回家继续,呵斥他们教训他们
You'll be home, yelling at themand,kicking their buttsbefore you know it.
这个孩子可能患了绝症,可他却关心自己的弟妹甚于自己
This kid might be facinga terminal disease,,and he's more worried abouthis brother and sister.
- 脑干正常,- 中脑没事
- brain stem's clean.,- Nothing in the midbrain.
那是什么?
What's that?
垂体前方 右上象限
The frontal lobe,upper-right quadrant.
我没看见什么
I don't see anything.
那儿
There.
很微小 但是..,我想是个肿瘤
It's tiny, but...,I think it's a tumor.
那种大小的应该可以手术
That size shouldbe excisable.
- 我们之前为什么没看见?,- 哦 天哪
- Why didn't wesee it earlier?,- Oh, god.
从轴线看 还有另一个,转换到下一切片
Axial view,there's another one.,Bring up the next slice.
到处都有
They're everywhere.
Jack的大脑有许多肿瘤形成的空洞,你知道他的反映吗?
jack's brainis riddled with tumors.,You knowwhat he's doing?
- 哀嚎?,- 给弟妹联系玩伴
- Moaning?,- Setting up play dates.
- 噢 真伟大! 有什么解释?,- 明显是因为
- Wow, what a guy!Theories?,- the obvious one.
脑部肿瘤摧毁了他的免疫系统,使感染有机可乘
Brain cancer destroyedhis immune system.,Left him wide openfor these infections.
House...,你真可怜
House...,you're pathetic.
你总是谈论病人的失败 伪善 懦弱
You'll analyze anyone's,faults,hypocrisies, weaknesses.
但是这孩子表现出了勇气,你就突然间只说医学的事了
But this kid's got some strength,and all of a sudden,there's no timeto talk about anythingbut the medicine.
他教会了青春期的孩子们一些真理,上帝不存在 生活很悲哀
He's teaching prepubescent kids that,truth matters,god doesn't, and life sucks.
我喜欢他,治疗方案?
I like him.,Treatment?
我们要给他放射性治疗
We need to start himon radiation.
那会摧毁他仅存的免疫系统
And destroy whatever's left,of his immune system.
但救了他的命!
and safe his life!
我知道自我牺牲的想法不适合你
I know the notion of self-sacrifice,is foreign to you.
你渴望看到他自我牺牲,是因为一旦有人那么做了
You wanna think that he'ssacrificing,himself because if one personcan do it,
你会认为世界不是那么冷漠了,人类也不再那么自私了
then maybe the worldisn't the cold,,selfish placeyou know that it is.
放射疗法会要他的命,还有别的吗?
Radiation could kill him.Alternatives?
*氢可酮*,(麻醉药品)
*HYDROCODONE*
没有选择了,根据他的肿瘤
There aren't any.,We saw the tumors.
我们可以不把那当作肿瘤
We could choose to say,they aren't tumors.
只是化脓
They're just pus.
那就能解释为什么昨天没看见
Which would explain why,they weren't there yesterday.
不可能是感染
It can't be an infection.
- 他注射过免疫球蛋白 广谱抗生素,- 确实
- He got ivig,broad spectrum antibiotics--,- exactly.
那为真菌繁殖创造了温床
It creates a perfect worldfor fungus.
搬进来 结个婚 再生一个小的
Moves in, gets married,has little fungi.
如果你那关于真菌的理论错误,你就是在浪费他仅有的一点时间
If you're wrongabout the fungus,,you're wasting what little timehe has left.
那也没损失什么,他的生活反正一团糟
Not a big sacrifice.,His life sucks.
所以让我们直接点,伸个针到孩子的大脑里去
So let's be right.,Go stick a needlein the kid's head.
如果吸出来的是脓 我是对的,我们也不必说什么
If you suck out a liquid,then I'm right,,and we haven'tanswered anything.
如果吸出来的是固体  你是对的,他再也不用操心玩伴了
If you suck out a solid, you're right,,and no more worrying about play dates.
好吧,我做你孩子的父亲
Okay, fine.,I'll father your child.
首先你得给我开一份维柯丁处方
First, you gotta write me,a vicodin prescription.
- 以便我能做足前戏,- 你还剩多少天的药?
- Just so I can getthrough the foreplay.,- How many daysyou have left?
嗯 大概能支持到下一分钟..
Ah, I could probably get throughmaybe...,next minute or so.
你来找我意味着那些小鸭子都不听话了,我很惊奇
And your coming to memeans your lackeys,actuallystood up to you-- I'm impressed.
- 是啊 他们的懦弱确实令我吃惊,- 你应该感谢他们
- Yes, their cowardiceis inspiring.,- Well, you should be thanking them.
如果他们妥协了 会被警察抓到证据,说你胁迫下属满足药瘾
If they caved,it'd give the cops evidence,that you intimidated underlingsto feed your addiction.
我可不爱写感谢信
I hate writingthank-you notes.
如果我请Cameron写感谢信,是不是太奇怪了?
Would it be weird if I,asked cameron to write them?
你在撮合我俩?
You're hooking me up?
不幸的是 如果我不给你开,警察就会说你不是真正需要止痛药
Unfortunately,if I cut you off,it'd give the cops evidence,that you don't reallyneed the pain meds.
我就知道那些只是烟雾弹,你真是个天才
I knew that cleavage was a smoke screen.,You're a genius.
- 你胳膊抬不起来,- 你还不能站着小便呢 给我
- You can't lift your arm.,- You can't pee standing up.Gimme.
你做过理疗了?,是不是该牵引--
You been doing physio?,Maybe you pulled--
是的 脱衣舞会上练过了,给我处方
yeah, been trainingfor pants off dance off.,Gimme the scrip.
你的肩膀问题并非生理上的
Your shoulder problemisn't physical.
把药方给我就能知道了--
Well, we'll find out if you ever give me the--
有什么新症状?  有什么不同?
what's new?What's different?
最近生活上有什么大的变化?,也许和爱人吵架?
Any big changesin your life recently?,A fight with the wife,maybe?
那是好事,说明你的肩膀是人类的
It's good.,Means your shoulder'sa human being.
开始的信号
It's a start.
- 我是对的 是吗?,- 是 只是没说中我
- I'm right, right?,- Yeah.Just not about me.
我的想法是对的  是不是?
I was right, right?
真菌感染造成脓肿  是曲霉
They were abscesses froma fungal infection.,Aspergillus.
但是我们仍旧不清楚原因
But we still have no idea why.
孩子的免疫系统天生有缺陷
Our kid's immune systemhas a factory defect.
- 是遗传性的,- 不可能是遗传性的
- It's genetic.,- It can't be genetiC.
那他从婴儿时期就会被感染的
He would have been getting,infections since he was an infant.
如果他在泡泡里长大就不会
Not if he grew upin a bubble.
或是他在火星长大,那也没有微生物
Or if he grew up on mars.,No germs there, either.
我不是指文字上的泡泡
I don't meana literal bubble.
父母的呵护相当于泡泡
A sweet, suburban bubble where mommies,and daddiesprotect their children.
父母死了 泡泡破了
They die, bubble bursts.
情感上的创伤引发的遗传疾病,问题是哪一种?
Continuing emotional trauma triggers,a genetic illness.Question is, which one?
感染种类的缩小限制了病因的可能性
The infections he's contracted,narrow down the possibilities.
甲肝说明可能是B淋巴细胞
Hep a indicates a problemwith his b cells.
- 布鲁顿氏低免疫球蛋白血症,- 艾肯菌
- Bruton's agammaglobulinemia?,- Eikenella.
补体缺乏
So a complement deficiency.
- 我有个病人 我需要--,- 现在不行!
- I have a patient.I need--,- not now!
- 我去!,- 你呆着
- I'll go.,- You'll stay.
- 病人快不行了,- 我的也是
- Patient's dying.,- So is mine.
至少不会下一个小时就死
Not in the next hour.
梅毒说明什么?
What does the syphilistell us?
说明什么?
What does it tell us?
或许是慢性肉芽肿
It could meanchronic granulomatous disease.
而且曲霉会破坏T细胞,会导致免疫缺陷
and the aspergillus is a t-cell issue.,Common variable immunodeficiency.
遗传病检测太费时间
Genetic testing'sgonna take time.
按照他现在感染的速度—
Given the rate he's picking up infections--
我们来比赛吧
why don't we turn itinto a race?
现在已经没时间让我们玩游戏
Little late to beplaying games with us.
不是你们, 是病菌
Not you guys.,The infections.
什么病菌?
What infections?
我们要给他的病菌
The infectionswe're gonna give him.
唯一能治的方法是让我病得更厉害?
The only way to cure meis to make me sicker?
四种可能的免疫缺陷,各自有其易感的病菌
Each of the four possiblegenetic conditions,is most susceptible to differenttypes of infection.
是什么?
What's that?
是由沙雷氏菌, 脑膜炎球菌,洋葱伯克氏菌和鼻病毒调制的鸡尾酒
This is a cocktailof serratia,,meningococcus,cepacia, and rhinovirus.
究竟哪种占优势将告诉我们需要的答案
Whichever germgains the most ground,plants the flagof its leader,gives us our answer.
你怎么知道哪种占了优势?
How are you gonna know,which onegains the most ground?
这是有趣的部分
Well, now,that's the fun part.
如果脑膜炎球菌占了优势, 你会抽搐
See, if the meningococcusis king of,the hill,you get to haveanother seizure.
沙雷氏菌会攻击你的肺部
The serratia willshut down your lungs.
如果是洋葱伯克氏菌,会发心脏病
If it's cepacia,you'll have a heart attack.
如果是鼻病毒,你会打喷嚏
If it's the rhinovirus,you'll sneeze.
不是每个病都那么吸引眼球,可以开始了?
Can't all be dramatic.,We good?
- 当然不,- 或者我们用猜的
- Hell, no.,- Well, the alternativeis we guess.
你的弟弟和妹妹再失去一个亲人,的可能性是3/4
And there's a threeout of four chancethat,your littlebrother and sisterwill get to cryover another coffin.
你在学校学过分数吧?,开始吗?
Did you study fractionsin school?,We good?
这种测试方法未经FDA批准
this testisn't exactly fda approved.
所以, 我们把这当作小秘密好吗?
So let's just keep itour little secret, okay?
"孤女安妮(音乐剧)"和"雾都孤儿",昨晚在大厅走廊上睡着了
Little orphan annieand oliver twist,slept in our hallwayslast night.
他们唱歌了吗?
Are they singing?
他们是孩子, 需要监护人
They're children.,They need a guardian.
找不到临时保姆
Couldn't find a babysitter.
因为他没法打电话,没法打电话因为他不能呼吸
On account of not being able to make any,phone callson account of notbeing able to breathe,
不能呼吸因为他的肺满布沙雷氏菌
on account of his lungs,filling up with serratia.
他得了慢性肉芽肿病
He has chronicgranulomatous disease.
游戏结束,我们该做的都做了
Game over.,Our work is done.
那么他会继续病着,你给儿童福利打电话
Then he's gonnakeep getting sick.,You gotta callsocial services.
骨髓移植将重启他的免疫系统
Bone marrow transplantwould,reboot his whole immune system.
他将活着赢得,本年度最悲惨老爸大奖
He'll behealthy enough to win,miserable daddyof the year.
如果她弟妹中有一个匹配
So see if one of his kidsis a match.
我的孩子们已经在检测他的弟妹
My kids are alreadytesting his kids.
- will的匹配,- 你检查了他?
- will's a match.,- You tested him?
- 我没同意--,- 只是抽血, 没危险
- I never consented--,- it's just a blood draw.There's no danger.
对于检查来说,那么手术呢?
To the testing.,What about the surgery?
will的危险? 一点没有
The risk for will?,It's next to nothing.
如果我不做这个手术呢?,有别的选择吗?
What if I don't do it?,What are my other options?
你的免疫系统不能打败病菌,我们每天都在接触
Your immune systemcan't fight offthe germs,we all come intocontact with every day.
现在我们知道了,可以有针对地采取措施
Now that we know,,we can use more targeted medications.
但是... 你还是会一直病下去
But...you'll stillget sick all the time.
- 你将出入医院--,- 但是我活着
- You'll be in and outof hospitals--,- but I'll live.
Jack...
你的寿命会大大缩短
your lifespan will be,substantially shortened.
你将病的再不能照顾你的弟妹了
And you'll be too sickto care,for your brotherand sister anymore.
你不能强迫他去--
You shouldn't havepressured him into--
- 没有强迫,- 他才八岁!
- there's no pressure.,- He's eight years old!
你对他说除非他帮他哥哥,否则他就死了, 你说他会怎么做?
You tell him his brother'sdying unless he helps,,what do you think he's gonna do?
- 他想帮你,- 他不知道
- He wants to help you.,- He has no idea.
你以为只是送出一件他的玩具
It's like you asked himto,let me playwith one of his toys.
这是手术, 他可能会死
This is surgery.,He could die.
他没事, 但你...
He'll be fine.,But you...
如果你死了, 就不能这样保护他了
you're gonna have a hard time,protecting him like thisif you're dead.
我接受移植
I'll do it.
当will18岁,可以自己做决定的时候
When will's 18,and can decide for himself.
- 高尚,- 低能
- Noble.,- Moronic.
同义词
It's a synonym.
你为什么不能接受,他想保护自己的弟弟?
Why can't you accepthe wants,to protect his brother?
他不得不保护,不是他想
Has to protect his brother.,He doesn't want to.
他想的是,尖叫着从责任边逃开
He wants to run screaming,from protecting his brother.
你是个伪君子
You're a hypocrite.
"证据就是一切","只有真相最重要"
Evidence is everything.,Truth is all that matters.
一旦说到人性,就全变了样
Except when it comesto people.
这孩子的所作所为证明你是错的
Everything we've learned about,this kidsays you're wrong.
但你不能接受
But you can't accept that.
否认诊断很容易
It's easy to rejectthe diagnosis.
放弃你的愤世嫉俗却没那么容易
Not so easy to reject your misanthropy.
因为那样你就要给别人一个战斗的机会
Because then you'd have to give,people a fighting chance.
那样就会...吓得你尿裤子
And that...,scares the crap out of you.
好
Okay.
让我们找点证据
Let's get some evidence.
你真幸运
It's your lucky day.
我刚找到另一个捐赠人,完全匹配
I just found another donor in the registry.,A perfect match.
我们可以做移植,没危险
We can do the transplant,,no danger to the rugrat.
你只需要在这签字
You just have to sign here.
除非另有原因你不想做
Unless there's another reason,you don't want it.
- 我可能死于手术,- 你可能因手术而生
- There's a chance I'd die.,- A chance you'll be cured.
可能你也不想要生
Maybe you don't want that,either.
可能待在医院里等待帮助
Maybe hanging outin a hospital,and getting waited on hand and foot
会让你记起以前,不用承担育儿责任的生活
reminds you of what life used to be like,before you were forcedto play mr. Mom.
我不想病
I don't like being sick.
但也不想健康
But you don't wantto be healthy either.
这是你摆脱的机会,不会内疚
This is your way out.,Guilt-free.
我说过will18得时候我会做
I said I'd do itwhen will's 18.
当他没有你也能照顾自己的时候
When he's ableto take care to himself.,Without you.
Jack...,你的弟妹需要你
Jack...,your brother and sisterneed you.
我知道!,每天每秒他们需要我
I know!I knowevery second of,every daythat they need me.
但我做他们的父亲太年轻了
But I'm too youngto be their dad!
你做得很好
Good for you.
别假装你惊讶
Don't pretendyou're surprised.
想去阳台上朝别人扔东西吗?
Wanna go throw stuff,at people off the balcony?
别这样, 邮件可以等会
Come on.,Mail can wait.
我在给病人推荐其他肿瘤医生,我关门大吉了
I'm referring my patients,to other oncologists.,I'm shutting downmy practice.
太好了!,我刚才还担心你会反应过度
Oh, good!'Cause I was afraid,you might overreact.
我不能让病人等着,只因为Cameron医生的老板不让她出来玩
I can't justask my patients to wait because,dr. Cameron's bosswon't let hercome out and play!
- 我只让你等了一个小时,- 三小时!
- I kept you waitingfor maybe an hour.,- Three hours!
- 有人死吗?,- 这次没有
- Did anybody die?,- Not this time.
Cameron现在有空了,想怎么用都行
Cameron's available now.,Use her all you want.
所以现在是毁掉我的生命的好时机?
Oh, so now's a better time,for me to have my lifetaken away?
- 这更符合你的日程表?,- 扮可怜
- It fits intoyour schedule better?,- Oh, poor you.
- 你以为声音大就可以--,- 你犯罪了!
- You think if you sufferloudly enough--,- you committed a crime!
你要我怎么做, 去自首?
What do you want me to do,turn myself in?
是! 是! 做点什么!,去自首! 表示一下悔恨！
Yes!Yes!Do something!,Go in!Show some remorse!
对Tritter说你会寻求帮助!
Tell tritteryou'll get some help!
我不需要帮助!
I don't need help!
House, 出去,出去
House, get out of here.,Get out of here.
我不会因Tritter对我们所做的...,产生负罪感
You are not gonna make mefeel guilty,about what tritteris doing...to us.
你已经有负罪感了
You already feel guilty.
你没来由的肩膀痛,并非因为手杖
Your mysterious shoulder pain,isn't coming from your cane.
源于你的良心
It's coming fromyour conscience.
以前这样也就够了
That used to be enough.
尽管你的言词恶毒,我知道你还在乎
Despite allyour smart-ass remarks,,I knew you gave a damn.
这次...
This time...
要么你帮我挺过这一关,要么就算了
you were either gonnahelp me,through this,or you weren't.
我找到了自己的答案
I got my answer.
谁送我去学校? 帮我做作业?
who's gonna drive me to school?,Help me with my homework?
有妈妈会带你去
There'll be a momwhere they take you.
一个真正的妈妈,可以做饭
A real mom.,Someone who can cook.
别担心, 我还可以见你们
Don't worry.,I'll still be ableto see you guys.
- 你说够能让他好点,- 对不起
- You saidyou'd make him better.,- I'm sorry.
谢谢你没告诉他们
Thank youfor not telling them.
你是个好孩子
You're a good kid.
从现在开始三个月...,六个月后...
Three months from now...,six months from now...
你会去见他们,你会舍不得离开
you'll be visiting them.,And you won't be ableto say good-bye.
你将告诉他们, 你曾经怯懦
You're gonna know you screwed up.
你将移植他的骨髓,把孩子要回来
You'll takehis bone marrow.,And you'lltake them back.
他们将成为你的负担
And they'll be a burdenand a pain.
你的生命将...,再不像常人的那样
And your life will...,never be what it was supposed to be.
但是你将为自己骄傲
But you'll beproud of yourself.
你的父母...,他们将为你骄傲
Your parents...,they'll be proud of you.
我不这么想
I don't think so.
这是我所愿意相信的
It's what I wanna believe.